{
    "subject": "resource/Felix_Hoffmann",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1868-01-21",
    "human_readable": "Felix Hoffmann was born on January 21st, 1868.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8821442723274231,
            "question": "When was Felix Hoffmann born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7673411965370178,
            "question": "Where was Felix Hoffmann born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6031027436256409,
            "question": "Was Felix Hoffmann a scientist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5960422158241272,
            "question": "What is Felix Hoffmann known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5329223871231079,
            "question": "Is there any information about Felix Hoffmann's family or early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4595282971858978,
            "question": "In what year did Felix Hoffmann come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4511886537075043,
            "question": "What significant contributions did Felix Hoffmann make?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3815072774887085,
            "question": "What field of study was Felix Hoffmann involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35362711548805237,
            "question": "What impact did Felix Hoffmann have on the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3031139671802521,
            "question": "Did Felix Hoffmann receive any awards or recognition for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Felix Hoffmann was born on January 21st, 1868.",
            "html": "dbpedia_696_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Felix Hoffmann have on the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_696_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study was Felix Hoffmann involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_696_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant contributions did Felix Hoffmann make?",
            "html": "dbpedia_696_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_696_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Felix Hoffmann was indeed born on January 21, 1868, in Ludwigsburg, Germany. This information is consistent across multiple documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}